https://shop.millermbz.com/privacy-agreement

Privacy Agreement | Millers Mercedes Benz Parts
REQUEST PRICE
Salutation (optional) Mrs. Mr. Mx.
I have read the datapolicy understand it and agree *
Fields with * are required
Send
To be able to use Millers Mercedes Benz Parts in full range, we recommend activating Javascript in your browser.
Service/Help
(RMA Form)
Newsletters Millers Star Moments Millers Customer Cruisers
Parts Catalogs Catalog Downloads New/Back In Stock Specials W121(190SL)(1955-1963) W113(230SL 250SL 280SL)(1963-1971) W107(280SL 350SL 380SL 450SL 560SL)(1972-1989) W129(SL300 SL320 SL500 SL600)(1990-2002) 180 190 219 220S 220SE 108 109 110 111 Chassis 114 115 116 123 126 Chassis 208 209 211 CHASSIS Rubber Kits Close Out Specials NOS Mercedes Parts
Catalog Downloads
Material Samples
Part/Price Request Form
About Us Contact Us
Login/Register
Call us: +1(714) 557-0115 Ext 102
Working time: Mon-Fri 8:00-18:00
Location:Phoenix, Arizona 85085
Information
(RMA Form)
Return Merchandise Authorization
Support Request
WholesaleLogin / Registration
Privacy Agreement What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: - To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)- To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)- To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) - To process transactions Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  - To send periodic emails The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.Do we use cookies? Yes, Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 09/15/2019sales@millermbz.com
Viewed
Newsletter
I have read the data protection information.
Wir versenden mit
Zahlungsmöglichkeiten
Parts Hotline
Parts Department Telephone: Call Mike1 (714) 557-0115 Ext 102Mon-Fri, 8 am - 6 pmAfter hours please leave a message
Additional Services
(RMA Form)
(RMA Form)
Return Merchandise Authorization
Support Request
WholesaleLogin / Registration
Realized with Shopware
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website.
More information
Accept
